http://www.equipmentandcontrols.com/about-us/privacy/

Hydrogen Plant
Pressure Swing Adsorption (PSA)
Water Quality Monitoring
Safety Instrumented Systems (SIS)
Produced Fluids Separation
Oil and Water Metering (Custody Transfer)
Hydrogen Plant
Pressure Swing Adsorption (PSA)
Water Quality Monitoring
Safety Instrumented Systems (SIS)
Produced Fluids Separation
Oil and Water Metering (Custody Transfer)
Customer Portal
Our website uses cookies. By continuing to browse our site you are agreeing to our Cookie Policy.
About Us
Privacy Policy
Your Privacy is Important to Us
To maintain our level of customer support, we (ECI) require certain information about our customers. ECI has taken measures to ensure the privacy and confidentiality of information we collect in accordance with the applicable state and federal privacy legislation.
ECI (including affiliates, divisions and related companies) is committed to controlling the collection, use and disclosure of personal information provided by you, our customer.
Personal Information We Collect
Personal information is information about you, the individual. It includes your contact information (i.e., first and last name, business address, business phone and fax number, business email address, etc.). and may also include data about the types of products, services and solutions you use or in which you have an interest. If you have attended any of our seminars or education sessions, it may also include your educational history with us. This information is used for the following purposes:
To establish and maintain responsible commercial relations with you and to provide you with ongoing customer service
To better understand your current and future needs
To communicate information about new products, services or solutions we think you may have an interest in
To alert you to important safety notices regarding products and services you may have purchased from us
Consent to Use Personal Information
Consent may be obtained in various ways. We may obtain your express consent, or we may determine that consent has been implied by the circumstances. For example, should you log in to our website and fill in the required form or reply to an e-mail, we would determine that consent has been given to use that information to serve your needs. Likewise, should you verbally provide personal information to an ECI employee, we would assume that consent to use this information is implied. In any case, we would safeguard this information against unauthorized use.
Since it is our culture and philosophy to respect our relationship with you, consent may be withdrawn by you at any time either verbally to an ECI employee, or by email: info@eci.us.
Sharing Personal Information with Others
We do not sell customer lists or personal information to others. In providing you with our products, solutions and services, we may need to disclose the personal information we collect to suppliers or subsidiaries. This is for the sole purpose of providing you with the right solution for your need and serving you better.
We may also use this information to assess your future needs and to offer the products and services that may best meet those needs. In these cases, should you not wish to hear from us in this manner, we will do our best to provide a simple method for you to have your name and information removed upon request. If you desire your name and address to be removed, contact us: info@eci.us.
How we Safeguard Personal Information
At ECI, we have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect our systems and personal information under our control against unauthorized access and use, and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage.
.
If we provide our suppliers with any personal information, we will advise them that suppliers are required to maintain customer confidentiality and may not use the information for any unauthorized purpose.
ECI employees and information system contractors we use are governed by standards and policies to ensure that personal information is secure and treated with care and respect. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and, although we will take steps to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted via the website; any transmission is therefore at your own risk.
Information Related to Website Use
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with useful content and services.
Personally identifiable information means any information collected online that could serve to identify you, such as, first and last name, physical address, email address, telephone number and any combination of personal information that could be used to determine identity. We collect personally identifiable information when you provide it to us, such as when you register on one of our sites, when you subscribe for an email newsletter or when you register to use certain services. Several of the services that we offer on our sites may require registration as a condition of use. Once you register with one of our ECI sites you are no longer anonymous to us. We may also receive information about you from other sources including our suppliers and add it to the information you provided to us.
Users who would rather not provide any of the information requested by our registration process will still be able to view the public access portions of our sites without registering.
Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of our sites. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit most of our sites, although active participation in certain areas of our sites may require cookies. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information, in which case we use that information to enhance the services provided to you in the ways described below.
You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.
We may use technologies, including electronic images--sometimes called transparent GIFs, clear GIFs, or beacons--that allow us to track general user traffic patterns. We may also automatically receive and record information from our servers and from your browser, including your IP address, the time of your visit to pages on our site, and information about pages you visited. Unless you have registered for one of our products or services, the information we gather through the use of tracking technologies cannot be matched with any personally identifiable information about you unless you have specifically given us personally identifiable information, in which case we use that information to enhance your services in the ways described below.
We use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including:
Keeping count of return visits to our sites
Accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on web site usage
Determining which features our overall user population use the most
We use the information we gather through our website for several purposes:
To enhance the user experience in our network of sites. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.
To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling users to participate in on-line registrations, message boards, etc.
To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding ECI's Privacy Policy, or if you desire to be removed from our mailing lists or have concerns as to the accuracy of information, please email info@eci.us.
